So now we are going to set up Mark three on Kali Linux.
So Kali Linux is an operating system for vulnerability testing.
You can install Kali Linux very easily.
Let me show it to you.
So all you have to do is you have to go to this link and you have to download torrent of this VMware
or VirtualBox, whatever software you want to use.
These are the two software which I use for creating virtual machines.
I'm using VMware, so you just have to download this torrent file and you can easily install Kali Linux,
right?
So it's quite easy to install.
I'm not going to show you how to install Kali Linux.
It's fairly simple, so I'll start on a fresh installation of Kali Linux.
So this is the fresh installation.
So let me open the terminal over here.
So this is the link, which is the documentation of Mark three.
You can go through this documentation as well.
So I'm going to show you how to install the tools of Mark three on Kali Linux.
So first of all, you have to download all the dependencies, the packages.
So you just have to copy all the packages as shown over here.
I'll copy and all you have to do is paste in your terminal and hit enter.
And it will ask you to install.
You just have to do.
Yes.
And it might take a few minutes to install.
It depends on your internet connection.
So all the dependencies are now installed.
So let's just proceed.
By the way, sometimes you might have to run this packages commands more than once because sometimes
it gives you an error on the first run or after some libraries.
So make sure if you get some error, you run this package, install command more than once.
So let's just proceed.
So now what we have to do is we have to do git clone of Proxmox three packages, so let's just copy
it.
And let's just face it.
So let me make the terminal a little.
Bigger so you can see it more clearly.
Let's just clear out and let's just do get clone.
Uh, from GitHub.
So these are the tools for Proxmox three.
Again, it might take a few minutes to install or to download.
It depends on your internet connection.
All right.
So Proxmox is also downloaded.
So let's just go into this directory.
Proxmox three.
And what we have to do is first we have to compile all these files.
So to compile, we have to use make command.
So we have to use make claim and then we have to make it all.
So we use make all and let's just hit enter.
So now it's compiling all the files for Proxmox three.
So the first compilation is done.
Now what we have to do is we have to go into the clients directory in the same folder.
So we are in Proxmox three now.
We will go to clients in the same directory, right?
So clients is in Mach three and then we have to make one more compile.
So we will just do Mac over here and it will compile all the files for Mach three for execution.
Right?
So now after this compilation, you will get this Mach three execution file, which we will run later
when we will plug our Mach three.
So that's all for this video.
In the next video, we are going to see how to update the firmware of Mach three.